In the previous few videos,
在之前的几个视频中，
Isa showed how to build an application using an llm
Isa展示了如何使用llm构建应用程序
from evaluating the inputs to processing the inputs
从评估输入到处理输入
to then doing final output checking before you show the output to the user.
再到在向用户显示输出之前进行最终输出检查。
After you've built such a system, how do you know how it's working?
构建这样的系统后，如何知道它的工作情况？
And maybe even as you deploy it and let users use it,
甚至在部署并让用户使用它时，
how can you track how it's doing
如何跟踪它的运行情况
and find any shortcomings and continue to improve
并发现任何缺陷并继续改进
the quality of the answers of your system?
系统的答案质量？
In this video, I'd like to share with you some best practices
在这个视频中，我想与您分享一些最佳实践
for evaluating the outputs of an llm.
用于评估llm的输出。
And I want to share with you specifically
我想特别与您分享
what it feels like to build one of these systems.
构建这些系统的感受。
One key distinction between what you hear me talk about in this video
您听到我在这个视频中谈论的一个关键区别
and what you may have seen in more traditional machine learning,
和您可能在更传统的机器学习中看到的区别，
supervised learning applications is because you can build
监督学习应用程序之间的区别在于，因为您可以快速构建
such an application so quickly, the methods for evaluating it,
这样的应用程序，评估它的方法，
it tends not to start off with a test set.
它通常不会从测试集开始。
Instead, you often end up gradually building up a set of test examples.
相反，您经常会逐渐建立一组测试示例。
Let me share with you what I mean by that.
让我与您分享我的意思。
You will remember this diagram from the second video
您将从第二个视频中记得这个图表
about how prompt-based development speeds up the core parts
关于如何基于提示开发加速核心部分
of model development from maybe months to just minutes or hours
的模型开发，从可能需要几个月到只需要几分钟或几小时
or at most a very small number of days.
或者最多只需要几天时间。
In the traditional supervised learning approach,
在传统的监督学习方法中，
if you needed to collect, say, 10,000 labeled examples anyway,
如果你需要收集，比如说，10,000个标记样本，
then the incremental cost of collecting another 1000 test examples
那么收集另外1000个测试样本的增量成本并不高。
isn't that bad.
所以在传统的监督学习环境中，
So in the traditional supervised learning setting,
收集一个训练集，
it was not unusual to collect a training set,
收集一个开发集或保留交叉验证集
collect a development set or holdout cross-validation set
在测试集中，然后在整个开发过程中使用它们。
in the test set, and then tap those at hand
但是如果你能够在几分钟内指定一个提示，
throughout this development process.
并在几个小时内得到一些工作成果，
But if you're able to specify a prompt in just minutes
那么如果你不得不暂停很长时间
and get something working in hours,
收集一千个测试样本，那将会是一个巨大的痛苦，
then it would seem like a huge pain
因为现在你可以在零个训练样本的情况下得到这个工作成果。
if you had to pause for a long time
因此，在使用LLM构建应用程序时，
to collect a thousand test examples
这通常是它的感觉。
because you can now get this working with zero training examples.
首先，你会在只有一到三到五个样本的小样本中调整提示，
So when building an application using an LLM,
并尝试让提示在它们身上起作用。
this is what it often feels like.
然后，当系统进行额外的测试时，
First, you would tune the prompts on just a small handful of examples,
你偶尔会遇到一些棘手的例子。
maybe one to three to five examples.
提示在它们身上不起作用，或者算法在它们身上不起作用。
And try to get a prompt that works on them.
这就是使用chatgpt api的开发者如何构建应用程序的过程。
And in that case, you can take these additional one or two
在这种情况下，您可以将这些额外的一个或两个
or three or five examples and add them to the set that you're testing on
或三个或五个示例添加到您正在测试的集合中
to just add additional tricky examples opportunistically.
以机会主义地添加其他棘手的示例。
Eventually, you have enough of these examples you've added
最终，您已经添加了足够的这些示例
to your slowly growing development set
到您缓慢增长的开发集中
that it becomes a bit inconvenient
它变得有点不方便
to manually run every example through the prompt
手动运行每个示例通过提示
every time you change the prompt.
每次更改提示时。
And then you start to develop metrics to measure performance
然后，您开始开发用于衡量性能的指标
on this small set of examples, such as maybe average accuracy.
在这些小示例集上，例如平均准确性。
And one interesting aspect of this process
这个过程的一个有趣方面
is if you decide at any moment in time
是如果您随时决定
your system is working well enough,
您的系统已经足够好了，
you can stop right there and not use it.
你可以停在那里不用它。
You can stop right there and not go on to the next bullet.
您可以在那里停下，不继续下一个项目。
And in fact, there are many deploy applications
事实上，有许多部署应用程序
that stops at maybe the first or the second bullet
停在第一或第二个项目
and are running just fine.
并且运行得非常好。
Now, if your hand-built development set
现在，如果您手动构建的开发集
that you're evaluating the model on
您正在评估模型的性能
isn't giving you sufficient confidence yet
还没有给您足够的信心
in the performance of your system,
在您的系统性能方面，
then that's when you may go to the next step
那么这就是您可能要采取的下一步
of collecting a randomly sampled set of examples
收集随机抽样的示例集
to tune the model to.
来调整模型。
And this would continue to be a development set
这将继续作为开发集
or a holdout cross-validation set,
或保留交叉验证集，
because it'd be quite common to continue to tune your prompt to this.
因为继续调整提示很常见。
And only if you need even higher fidelity estimate
只有当您需要更高保真度的估计时，
of the performance of your system,
您的系统的性能，
then might you collect and use a holdout test sets
那么您可能会收集并使用保留测试集
that you don't even look at yourself
您自己不看
when you're tuning the model.
当您调整模型时。
And so, step four tends to be more important
因此，如果您的系统91％的时间得到正确答案，
if, say, your system is getting the right answer 91% of the time,
您想将其调整为92％的正确答案
and you want to tune it to get it to give the right answer 92%
和你想要的93％，
or 93% of the time,
那么您确实需要更多的示例
then you do need a larger set of examples
测量91％和93％性能之间的差异。
to measure those differences between 91% and 93% performance.
然后只有当您真正需要一个无偏，
And then only if you really need an unbiased,
公平的估计系统如何运行时，
fair estimate of how was the system doing,
那么您需要超越开发集
then do you need to go beyond the development set
也收集保留测试集。
One important caveat,
一个重要的警告，
I've seen a lot of applications of large language models
我看到了许多大型语言模型的应用
where there isn't meaningful risk of harm
在其中没有实质性的风险
if it gives not quite the right answer.
如果它没有给出完全正确的答案。
But obviously, for any high-stakes applications,
但是，对于任何高风险应用，
if there's a risk of bias or an inappropriate output
如果存在偏见或不适当的输出的风险
causing harm to someone,
对某人造成伤害，
then the responsibility to collect a test set
那么收集测试集的责任
to rigorously evaluate the performance of your system
严格评估系统的性能
to make sure it's doing the right thing before you use it,
确保在使用之前它能够做正确的事情，
that becomes much more important.
这变得更加重要。
But if, for example,
但是，例如，
if you are using it to summarize articles
如果你正在使用它来总结文章
just for yourself to read and no one else,
只是为了自己阅读而不是别人，
then maybe the risk of harm is more modest,
那么可能造成的危害风险更小，
and you can stop early in this process
你可以在这个过程中早早停止
without going to the expense of bullets four and five
而不必去花费收集更大数据集的代价。
of collecting larger data sets on which to evaluate your algorithm.
因此，在这个例子中，
So in this example,
让我从通常的辅助函数开始。
let me start with the usual helper functions.
使用一个工具函数来获取产品和类别列表。
Use a utils function to get a list of products and categories.
在计算机和笔记本电脑类别中，
So in the computers and laptop category,
有一些计算机和笔记本电脑的清单。
there's a list of computers and laptops.
在智能手机和配件类别中，
In the smartphones and accessories category,
这是一些智能手机和配件的清单，
here's a list of smartphones and accessories,
以此类推其他类别。
and so on for other categories.
现在，假设一个地址的任务是给出用户输入，
Now, let's say the task of an address is given a user input,
例如，如果我预算有限，我可以买什么电视
such as what TV can I buy if I'm on a budget
以检索相关的类别和产品，
to retrieve the relevant categories and products
以便我们有正确的信息来回答用户的查询。
so that we have the right info to answer the user's query.
这样我们就可以回答用户的问题了。
So here's a prompt.
这是一个提示。
Feel free to pause the video
如果你愿意，可以随时暂停视频
and read through this in detail if you wish.
并详细阅读这些内容。
But the prompt specifies a set of instructions,
但提示指定了一组指令，
and it actually gives the language model
实际上它给了语言模型
one example of a good output.
一个好的输出示例。
This is sometimes called a few-shot
这有时被称为几次提示
or technically one-shot prompting
或技术上的一次提示
because we're actually using a user message
因为我们实际上使用了用户消息
and a system message to give it one example of a good output.
和系统消息来给它一个好的输出示例。
If someone says, I want the most expensive computer,
如果有人说，我想要最贵的电脑，
let's just return all the computers
让我们返回所有的电脑
because we don't have pricing information.
因为我们没有定价信息。
Now, let's use this prompt on the customer message,
现在，让我们在客户消息上使用这个提示，
which TV can I buy if I'm on a budget?
如果我预算有限，我可以买哪种电视？
And so we're passing in to this both the prompt,
因此，我们将提示，
customer message zero, as well as the products and category.
客户消息零，以及产品和类别传递给它。
This is the information that we have retrieved up top
这是我们在上面检索到的信息
using the utils function.
使用utils函数。
And here it lists out the relevant information to this query,
这里列出了与此查询相关的相关信息，
which is under the category televisions
这是在电视类别下的
and whole theater systems.
和整个剧院系统。
This is a list of TVs and whole theater systems
这是一个看起来相关的电视和整个剧院系统的列表
that seem relevant.
。
To see how well the prompt is doing,
要查看提示的效果如何，
you may evaluate it on a second prompt.
您可以在第二个提示上进行评估。
Customer says I need a charger for my smartphone.
客户说我需要一个智能手机充电器。
It looks like it's correctly retrieving this data.
看起来它正在正确地检索这些数据。
Category smartphones and accessories,
类别是智能手机和配件，
and it lists the relevant products
它列出了相关的产品
and here's another one.
这是另一个例子。
So what computers do you have?
那么你有哪些电脑？
And hopefully you'll retrieve a list of the computers.
希望你能检索到电脑的列表。
So here I have three prompts.
所以我有三个提示。
And if you are developing this prompt for the first time,
如果你是第一次开发这个提示，
it would be quite reasonable to have one or two
有一个或两个或三个这样的例子是相当合理的，
or three examples like this,
并且不断调整提示，
and to keep on tuning the prompt
直到它给出适当的输出，
until it gives appropriate outputs,
直到提示检索到相关的产品和类别
until the prompt is retrieving the relevant products
对于你所有的提示，
and categories to the customer requests
在这个例子中的所有三个提示。
for all of your prompts,
如果提示缺少一些产品或其他东西，
all three of them in this example.
那么我们可能会回去编辑提示几次，直到它做对了
And if the prompt had been missing some products
如果提示失败了，那么我们可能会回去编辑提示几次，直到它做对了
or something, then what we would do is probably go back
在这里是一个提示的例子。
to edit the prompt a few times until it gets it right
告诉我关于SmartX配置文件和Philips Now相机的信息，
on all three of these prompts.
在这三个提示中都是如此。
After you've gotten the system to this point,
在你把系统带到这个地步之后，
you might then start running the system in testing,
你可能会开始在测试中运行系统，
maybe send it to internal test users
也许把它发送给内部测试用户
or try using it yourself
或者尝试自己使用它
and just run it for a while to see what happens.
并运行一段时间看看会发生什么。
And sometimes you will run across a prompt
有时你会遇到一个提示
that it fails on.
它会失败。
So here's an example of a prompt.
这是一个提示的例子。
Tell me about the SmartX profile and the Philips Now camera,
告诉我关于SmartX配置文件和Philips Now相机的信息，
also what TVs you have.
还有你有哪些电视。
So when I run it on this prompt,
所以当我在这个提示符上运行它时，
it looks like it's outputting the right data,
它看起来像是输出了正确的数据，
but it also outputs a bunch of text here,
但它也输出了一堆文本，
this extra junk.
这些是多余的。
It makes it harder to parse this into a Python list of dictionaries.
这使得将其解析为Python字典列表更加困难。
So we don't like that it's outputting this extra junk.
所以我们不喜欢它输出这些多余的东西。
So when you run across one example that the system fails on,
所以当你遇到一个系统无法处理的例子时，
then common practice is to just note down
常见的做法就是记录下来
that this is a somewhat tricky example.
这是一个有点棘手的例子。
So let's add this to our set of examples
所以让我们将其添加到我们要系统地测试的示例集中。
that we're going to test the system on systematically.
如果你继续运行系统一段时间，
And if you keep on running the system for a while longer,
也许它会在这些示例上工作。
maybe it works on those examples.
我们已经调整了提示符以适应三个示例，
so maybe it will work on many examples.
所以它可能会在许多示例上工作。
But just by chance, you might run across another example
但仅仅是偶然，你可能会遇到另一个例子
where it generates an error.
它会生成一个错误。
So this customer message for also causes the system
所以这个“also”客户消息会导致系统
to output a bunch of junk text at the end that we don't want.
在末尾输出一堆我们不想要的垃圾文本。
Trying to be helpful to get all this extra text,
试图提供所有这些额外的文本，
but we actually don't want this.
但我们实际上不想要这些。
And so at this point, you may have run this prompt
所以在这一点上，你可能已经运行了这个提示符
maybe on hundreds of examples, maybe your test users,
也许是在数百个示例上，也许是在你的测试用户上，
but you would just take the examples,
但你只需要拿这些示例，
the tricky ones it's doing poorly on,
它表现不佳的棘手问题，
and now have this set of five examples indexed from zero to four,
现在有了这组从零到四索引的五个示例，
have this set of five examples that you use
有了这组你使用的五个示例
to further fine tune the prompts.
进一步微调提示。
And in both of these examples,
在这两个示例中，
the LM had output a bunch of extra junk text
LM输出了一堆我们不想要的额外垃圾文本
at the end that we don't want.
在结尾处。
And after a little bit of trial and error,
经过一些试错，
you might decide to modify the prompts as follows.
您可能会决定按以下方式修改提示。
So here's a new prompt.
这是一个新提示。
This is called prompt V2.
这称为提示V2。
But what we did here was we added to the prompt,
但我们在提示中添加了以下内容，
do not output any additional text that's not in JSON format,
不要输出任何不在JSON格式中的附加文本，
just to emphasize, please don't output this JSON stuff,
强调一下，请不要输出这些JSON内容，
and added a second example using the user
并添加了第二个示例，使用用户和助手消息进行few-shot提示，
and assistant message for few-shot prompting,
其中用户询问最便宜的计算机。
where the user asked the cheapest computer.
在这两个few-shot示例中，
And in both of the few-shot examples,
我们向系统演示了一个仅输出JSON的响应。
we're demonstrating to the system a response
因此，这是我们刚刚添加到提示中的额外内容，
where it gives only JSON output.
不要放置任何不在JSON格式中的附加文本。
So here's the extra thing that we just added to the prompt,
我们使用few-shot user one，few-shot assistant one，
do not put any additional text that's not in JSON format.
和few-shot user two，few-shot assistant two，
And we use few-shot user one, few-shot assistant one,
为其提供了两个这些few-shot提示。
So let me hit shift enter to find that prompt.
所以让我按shift enter查找那个提示符。
And you were to go back and manually rerun this prompt
如果你回去手动重新运行这个提示符，
on all five of the examples of user inputs,
在所有五个用户输入示例中重新运行它，
including this one that previously had given a broken output,
包括之前输出错误的这个示例，
you find that it now gives a correct output.
你会发现它现在输出正确了。
And if you were to go back and rerun this new prompt,
如果你回去重新运行这个新的提示符，
this is prompt version V2, on that customer message example
这是提示符版本V2，在那个导致输出错误的客户消息示例上，
that had resulted in the broken output
它会生成更好的输出。
with extra junk after the JSON output,
有了JSON输出后面的额外垃圾，
then this will generate a better output.
那么这将生成更好的输出。
And I'm not going to do it here,
我不会在这里做这件事，
but I encourage you to pause the video
但我鼓励你暂停视频，
and rerun it yourself on customer message four
并在客户消息四上重新运行它自己
as well on this prompt V2,
以及这个提示符V2，
see if it also generates the correct output.
看看它是否也生成了正确的输出。
And hopefully it will, I think it should.
希望它会，我认为它应该会。
And of course, when you modify the prompts,
当然，当你修改提示符时，
it's also useful to do a bit of regression testing
做一些回归测试也是有用的，
to make sure that when fixing the incorrect outputs
以确保在修复提示符三和四的不正确输出时，
on prompts three and four,
它不会破坏提示符零的输出。
it didn't break the outputs on prompt zero either.
现在，你可以看出来，如果我必须复制粘贴五个提示符，
Now, you can kind of tell that if I had to copy paste five prompts,
例如零、一、二、三和四，
customer such as zero, one, two, three, and four,
到我的Jupyter Notebook中并运行它们，
into my Jupyter Notebook and run them
然后手动查看它们是否正在输出。
the right categories and products, you can kind of do it.
通过正确的分类和产品，你可以做到这一点。
I can look at this and go, yep, category TV
我可以看到这个，然后说，是的，电视类别，
and home theater systems products.
和家庭影院系统产品。
Yep, looks like you got all of them.
是的，看起来你都有了。
But it's actually a little bit painful to do this manually,
但是手动完成这个过程有点痛苦，
to manually inspect or to look at this output,
手动检查或查看这个输出，
to make sure with your eyes that this is exactly the right output.
用你的眼睛确保这是完全正确的输出。
So when the development set that you're tuning to
因此，当你要调整的开发集不仅仅是一小部分示例时，
becomes more than just a small handful of examples,
开始自动化测试过程就变得有用了。
it then becomes useful to start to automate the testing process.
这里有一组10个示例
where I'm specifying 10 customer messages.
我在这里指定了10个客户留言。
So here's the customer message, what TV can I buy from a budget,
这是客户留言，我可以从预算中购买什么电视，
as well as what's the ideal answer.
以及什么是理想的答案。
Think of this as the right answer in the test set,
把它看作是测试集中的正确答案，
or really, I should say development set,
或者真正应该说是开发集，
because we're actually tuning to this.
因为我们实际上正在调整它。
And so we've collected here 10 examples indexed from zero through nine,
因此，我们在这里收集了10个示例，从零到九进行索引，
where the last one is if the user says,
最后一个是如果用户说，
I would like hot tub time machine, we have no relevant products to that,
我想看热水浴缸时光机，我们没有相关产品，
really sorry. So the ideal answer is the empty set.
真的很抱歉。因此，理想的答案是空集。
And now, if you want to evaluate automatically,
现在，如果你想自动评估，
what a prompt is doing on any of these 10 examples,
在这10个示例中，提示正在做什么，
here is a function to do so. It's kind of a long function.
这里有一个函数可以实现这个功能。这是一个有点长的函数。
Feel free to pause the video and read through it if you wish.
如果你愿意，可以随时暂停视频并阅读它。
But let me just demonstrate what it is actually doing.
但是让我演示一下它实际上在做什么。
So let me print out the customer message for customer message zero.
所以让我打印出客户信息零的客户信息。
Right, so customer messages,
对，客户信息，
which TV can I buy if I'm on a budget?
如果我预算有限，我应该买哪种电视？
And let's also print out the ideal answer.
让我们也打印出理想的答案。
So the ideal answer is here are all the TVs
所以理想的答案是这里是所有的电视
that we want the prompt to retrieve.
我们希望提示检索的。
And let me now call the prompt.
现在让我调用提示。
This is prompt V2 on this customer message
这是这个客户信息上的提示 V2
with that user products and category information.
带有用户产品和类别信息。
Let's print it out.
让我们打印出来。
And then we'll call the eval responsive ideal function
然后我们将调用 eval responsive ideal 函数
to see how well the response matches the ideal answer.
看看响应与理想答案的匹配程度。
And in this case, it did output the category that we wanted
在这种情况下，它输出了我们想要的类别
and it did output the entire list of products.
并输出了整个产品列表。
And so this gives you the score of 1.0.
这给你得分为 1.0。
Just to show you one more example,
再给你展示一个例子，
it turns out that I know it gets it wrong on example seven.
结果我知道它在第七个例子上做错了。
So if I change this from zero to seven and run it,
所以如果我把这个从零改成七并运行它，
this is what it gets.
这就是它得到的结果。
Oh, let me update this to seven as well.
哦，让我也把这个更新为七。
So under this customer message, this is the ideal answer
所以在这个客户信息下，这是理想的答案
where it should output under gaming consoles and accessories.
它应该在游戏机和配件下输出。
So this is gaming consoles and accessories.
这是游戏机和配件。
But whereas the response here has three outputs,
但是这里的响应有三个输出，
it actually should have had one, two, three, four, five outputs.
实际上应该有一个、两个、三个、四个、五个输出。
And so it's missing some of the products.
所以它缺少了一些产品。
So what I would do if I'm tuning the prompt now is I would then
所以如果我现在调整提示，我会使用一个for循环来循环遍历所有10个开发集示例
use a for loop to loop over all 10 of the development set examples
在这里我们反复提取客户信息，
where we repeatedly pull out the customer message,
获取理想答案，正确答案，
get the ideal answer, the right answer,
调用arm获取响应，进行评估，
call the arm to get a response, evaluate it,
然后，你知道的，累积平均值。
and then, you know, accumulate it in average.
让我来运行一下。
And let me just run this.
好的。
All right.
所以这将需要一段时间来运行，
So this will take a while to run,
但是当它运行完毕时，这就是结果。
but when it's done running, this is the result.
我们正在运行这10个示例。
We're running through the 10 examples.
看起来第七个示例是错误的。
It looks like example seven was wrong.
所以10个示例中正确的比例为90%。
And so if you were to tune the prompts,
所以如果你需要调整提示，
you can rerun this to see if the percent correct goes up or down.
你可以重新运行这个程序，看看正确的百分比是上升还是下降。
What you just saw in this notebook
你刚刚在这个笔记本中看到了这个公告列表的第一、二、三步。
is going through steps one, two, and three of this bulletin list.
这已经给出了一个相当不错的10个示例的开发集，
And this already gives a pretty good development set of 10 examples
用于调整和验证提示是否有效。
with which to tune and validate the prompts is working.
如果你需要更高的严谨性，
If you needed an additional level of rigor,
那么你现在拥有了所需的软件。
to collect a randomly sampled set of maybe 100 examples
收集大约100个随机样本
with their ideal outputs,
以及它们的理想输出，
and maybe even go beyond that to the rigor of a holdout test set
甚至可以超越一个保留测试集的严谨性
that you don't even look at while you're tuning the prompt.
在你调整提示时，你甚至不看它。
But for a lot of applications, stopping at bullet three,
但对于许多应用程序，停留在第三个要点，
but there are also certainly applications
但也肯定有应用程序
where you could do what you just saw me do in this Jupyter notebook,
你可以像在这个Jupyter笔记本中看到的那样做，
and they get a pretty performance system quite quickly.
并且很快就可以得到一个相当好的性能系统。
With, again, the important caveat that,
再次强调，重要的是，
if you're working on a safety critical application
如果你正在处理一个安全关键应用程序
or an application where there's non-trivial risk of harm,
或者一个存在非微不足道风险的应用程序，
then of course, it would be the responsible thing to do
那么当然，负责任的做法是
to actually get a much larger test set
在使用它之前获得一个更大的测试集
to really verify the performance before you use it anywhere.
以确实验证性能。
And so that's it.
就是这样。
I find that the workflow of building applications using prompts
我发现使用提示构建应用程序的工作流程
is very different than a workflow of building applications
与使用监督学习构建应用程序的工作流程非常不同。
using supervised learning.
因此，我认为这是需要记住的一件好事
And so I think that's a good thing to keep in mind
当你正在构建监督学习时。
when you're building supervised learning.
迭代的速度感觉要快得多。
And the pace of iteration feels much faster.
如果你还没有这样做过，
And if you have not yet done it before,
你可能会惊讶于一个评估方法
you might be surprised at how well an evaluation method
仅建立在一些手工策划的棘手例子上的表现如何。
You think with 10 examples,
你可能认为只有10个例子是不具有统计学意义的。
and this is not statistically valid for almost anything.
但当你实际使用这个过程时，你可能会惊讶于添加一些棘手的例子到开发集中的有效性。
But you might be surprised when you actually use this procedure,
但你可能会惊讶于当你实际使用这个过程时，
how effective adding a handful,
添加一些棘手的例子到开发集中的有效性。
just a handful of tricky examples into development sets
这对于帮助你和你的团队找到有效的提示和有效的系统非常有帮助。
in terms of helping you and your team
在这个视频中，输出可以定量评估，
get to an effective set of prompts and effective system.
就像有一个期望的输出一样，你可以判断它是否给出了这个期望的输出。
In this video, the outputs could be evaluated quantitatively,
因此，在下一个视频中，让我们看看如何在这种更加模糊的情况下评估我们的输出。
as in there was a desired output,
在那种情况下，什么是正确答案是有点模糊的。
and you could tell if it gave this desired output or not.
接下来，让我们看看如何在这种更加模糊的情况下评估我们的输出。
So the next video, let's take a look at how you can evaluate
在下一个视频中，让我们看看如何评估我们的输出，
our outputs in that setting where what is the right answer
在这种情况下，什么是正确答案是有点模糊的。
is a bit more ambiguous.
在下一个视频中，让我们看看如何在这种更加模糊的情况下评估我们的输出。